[Music]
WD group as you know is a pan Asian um
insurer. We operate in 10 markets but at
the same time we cannot forget why we
are here for we are all about changing
the way people feel about insurance and
how are we going to do that if our
customers don't feel that on a
day-to-day basis. You can talk talk talk
talk about it but they need to feel it
on a day-to-day basis and that's what
drives me on a day-to-day basis coming
to FWD because that's our vision.
Everybody is doing cloud but it's the
way we have done it right. So we have
not just done a lift and shift we also
rationalize application when we were
doing it. We put in the cloud centers of
excellence from the beginning. We put
group landing zone. It doesn't matter
it's it's Azure or AWS. We created a
group landing zone so that we can manage
using the one uh you know place. Uh we
were at 27% cloud adoption and within 3
years we were 92% and today we are 98%
and very soon going to be 100% by end of
the year. Late last last year or early
last year, we renewed the five-year
commitment with AWS and that partnership
is very strategic partnership for us
simply because
50% of our workload is on AWS. It's a
considerable amount of chunk of our
workload is in AWS and it's growing. One
of the thing I'm very passionate about
why did we move to cloud very fast is
because Microsoft and AWS will will do
far more better job of doing a
sustainable greenhouse uh managed data
center as compared to ours ever would be
early 2024 we launched our four platform
strategy basically our the customer
platform is Omni our the operations
platform it was operations platform for
us it's more more like a modular and
that's the fourth platform form which is
we call it as one modularity. So one
modularity in a way encapsulates all the
other three platform and I call it is
platform of the platform. So rather than
becoming a application, we became a
ecosystemled a platformled play.
[Music]